Guide to the Frank Clyde Brown papers, 1912-1974 RL.00160
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Cylinders and Discs, 10 boxes
  - Phonodiscs, 1936-1941
    - RL00160-PD-0010_02, 1936-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0010_02)
      Title: Lord I Can't Sit Down, performer: Crosby, Louis | White, James | Winstead, Newman | Wolven, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:54:542
    - RL00160-PD-0011_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0011_01)
      Title: Little Mohee, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:28:547
      Title: Old Ship of Zion, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:34:912
    - RL00160-PD-0011_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0011_02)
      Title: Edward Lewis, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:33:516
    - RL00160-PD-0012_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0012_01)
      Title: Banjo Music, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:12:673
      Title: Oh I'm out here for the last time..., performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:50:542
      Title: Goodbye to the Cracking of the Pistols, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:34:733
      Title: Standing by the Old Cabin Door, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:02:10:191
    - RL00160-PD-0012_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0012_02)
      Title: Old Raccoon, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:19:830
      Title: Rainbow Division, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:18:783
      Title: Old Smokey, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:53:975
      Title: Instrumental, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:06:553
    - RL00160-PD-0013_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0013_01)
      Title: Instrumental with fiddles, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:28:481
      Title: Instrumental with fiddles, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:12:767
      Title: Instrumental with fiddles, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:16:341
      Title: Instrumental with fiddles, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:42:571
    - RL00160-PD-0013_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0013_02)
      Title: Maggie Dear, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:02:28:828
      Title: Instrumental with fiddles, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:34:308
      Title: Instrumental with fiddles, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:32:564
    - RL00160-PD-0014_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0014_01)
      Title: Flute Music, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:58:563
      Title: Down In the Valley to Pray, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:18:763
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:10:905
      Title: Wife of Usher's Well, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:02:18:980
    - RL00160-PD-0014_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0014_02)
      Title: Fiddle music, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:05:477
      Title: Fiddle music, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:03:885
      Title: Fiddle music, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:07:486
      Title: Fiddle music, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:10:985
      Title: Fiddle music, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:47:729
    - RL00160-PD-0015_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0015_01)
      Title: Pretty Fair Maid Down In the Garden, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:02:48:950
      Title: Little Mohea, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:02:29:613
    - RL00160-PD-0015_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0015_02)
      Title: Young Charlotte, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:03:28:503
      Title: Black Jack Davy, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:59:774
    - RL00160-PD-0016_01, 1939-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0016_01)
      Title: Hog Drovers, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:30:486
      Title: Darling Caisy Dean, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:56:970
      Title: Black Sally, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:42:324
      Title: Lord Lovel, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:18:756
      Title: The Twa Sisters (Old Man From the North Country) [false start], performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:05:10:455
      Title: Sourwood Mountain, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:22:910
    - RL00160-PD-0016_02, 1939-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0016_02)
      Title: Oh Drowsy Sleeper, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:29:703
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:56:277
      Title: Sourwood Mountain, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:52:203
      Title: Old Rattler, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:36:671
    - RL00160-PD-0017_01, 1939-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0017_01)
      Title: Our Good Man, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:23:274
      Title: Venison (Hunting Song), performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:23:742
      Title: Darby's Ram, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:39:489
      Title: The Blind Child (Girl), performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:12:895
      Title: The Fatal Wedding Bells, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:43:775
      Title: Billy Boy, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:20:374
    - RL00160-PD-0017_02, 1939-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0017_02)
      Title: Blue Ridge Mountain Blues, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:33:998
      Title: The Boston Burgular, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:44:575
      Title: I'm as Free as a Little Bird, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:20:472
      Title: Just Break the News to Mother, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:43:278
      Title: Old Joe Clark, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:30:371
    - RL00160-PD-0018_01, 1939-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0018_01)
      Title: The Little Mohee, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:36:966
      Title: Louise, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:12:035
      Title: Song of the Sunny South, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:49:006
      Title: I Offer This Hand of Mine, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:12:001
    - RL00160-PD-0018_02, 1939-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0018_02)
      Title: Lulu Falls, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:54:611
      Title: Mae, Dearest Mae, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:30:351
      Title: Kingdom Coming (Massa's Gone Away), performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:29:819
      Title: Somebody's Knocking at Your Do', performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:05:183
      Title: Somebody's Waiting For Me, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:45:900
      Title: There is No One Like Mother to Me, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:19:184
    - RL00160-PD-0019_01, 1939-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0019_01)
      Title: Lover's Return, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:08:431
      Title: Golden Bells, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:02:042
      Title: Raindrop Waltz [Instrumental], performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:32:364
      Title: Spanish Fandango [Instrumental], performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:43:268
      Title: Lonesome Road Blues [Instrumental], performer: Kuykendall, Otis | Robinson, G.S., location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:25:313
      Title: John Henry, performer: Robinson, G.S. | Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:55:881
    - RL00160-PD-0019_02, 1939-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0019_02)
      Title: John Henry, performer: Robinson, G.S., location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:29:037
      Title: The Man From Arkansas, performer: Robinson, G.S. | Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:52:759
      Title: He Never Came Back, performer: Robinson, G.S. | Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:27:667
      Title: The Dying Cow Girl, performer: Robinson, G.S. | Kuykendall, Otis, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:03:525
    - RL00160-PD-0020_01, 1939-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0020_01)
      Title: The Red, White, and Blue, performer: Robinson, G.S., location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:39:878
      Title: Sorghum Molasses, performer: Robinson, G.S., location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:19:882
      Title: In The Shade of the Old Apple Tree, performer: Robinson, G.S., location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:57:481
      Title: The Kicking Mule, performer: Robinson, G.S., location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:27:651
    - RL00160-PD-0020_02, 1939-07-19 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0020_02)
      Title: I Wish That Gal Was Mine, performer: Robinson, G.S., location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:04:961
      Title: Darling Chloe, performer: Robinson, G.S., location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:22:175
      Title: The Cruel Brother (O Lily O), performer: Gordon, Becky, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:01:717
      Title: Lord Thomas and Fair Annet (Lord Thomas), performer: Gordon, Becky, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:10:347
      Title: Pretty Fair Maid (Fair Maiden In a Garden), performer: Gordon, Becky, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:18:627
    - RL00160-PD-0021_01, 1939-07-29 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0021_01)
      Title: Little Musgrove and Lady Barnard (Little Matthy Groves), performer: Walker, Edith, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:05:01:974
      Title: James Harris (Housecarpenter), performer: Michael, Chloe, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:24:692
      Title: Gypsie Laddie (Black Jack Davy), performer: Michael, Chloe, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:13:121
    - RL00160-PD-0021_02, 1939-07-19 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0021_02)
      Title: The Silk Merchant's Daughter, performer: Gordon, Becky, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:41:471
      Title: Lord Randal (Ransome), performer: Gordon, Becky, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:21:461
      Title: James Harris (Housecarpenter), performer: Gordon, Becky, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:21:489
      Title: Lady Isabel and the Elf Knight (Lady Isabel), performer: Gordon, Becky, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:47:095
      Title: Drinking Song, performer: Gordon, Becky, location: Asheville (N.C.) | Buncombe County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:00:548
    - RL00160-PD-0022_01, 1939-07-24 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0022_01)
      Title: Jack and the Old Rich Man [Prose Tale], performer: Proffitt, Frank, location: unknown, running time: 00:10:33:767
    - RL00160-PD-0022_02, 1939-07-30 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0022_02)
      Title: Lord Thomas and Fair Annet (Fair Ellender, or The Brown Girl), performer: McGuire, G., location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:07:059
      Title: Lady Isabel and the Elf Knight, performer: Church, Jamie, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:57:987
      Title: The Sinking of the Titanic, performer: Church, Jamie, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:05:142
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: Trivette, John, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:17:563
    - RL00160-PD-0023_01, 1939-08-10 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0023_01)
      Title: The Farmer's Curst Wife (The Woman and the Devil), performer: Church, Jamie, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:30:501
      Title: Young Charlotte (Fair Charlotte), performer: Church, Minnie, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:05:01:931
      Title: Gypsie Laddie (Black Jack Davy), performer: Church, Jamie, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:33:689
      Title: The Golden Glove (Young Caroline Was a Lady), performer: Trivette, John, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:57:392
    - RL00160-PD-0023_02, 1939-08-10 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0023_02)
      Title: George Collins, performer: Church, Jamie | Church, Minnie | Webb, Pearle, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:57:298
      Title: The Drunkard's Home, performer: Church, Jamie | Church, Minnie | Webb, Pearle, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:44:808
      Title: The Bloody Miller (The Cruel Miller), performer: Trivette, John, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:41:036
      Title: Lillie Shaw, performer: Church, Jamie, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:29:452
      Title: Young Hunting (Oh Henery), performer: Church, Jamie | Trivette, John, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:49:763
    - RL00160-PD-0024_01, 1939-08-14 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0024_01)
      Title: Wicked Polly, performer: Church, Minnie, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:04:290
      Title: Pretty Polly, performer: Church, Jamie, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:47:132
      Title: Hick's Farewell, performer: Church, G.F. (Grandpa), location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:22:938
      Title: The Twelve Days of Christmas, performer: Watson, G.M., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:35:367
      Title: Pretty Polly, performer: Watson, Faye, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:23:049
    - RL00160-PD-0024_02, 1939-08-14 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0024_02)
      Title: Pretty Polly [Cuckoo verse], performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:59:963
      Title: The Rake and the Rambling Boy, performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:22:237
      Title: Young Beichan (Lord Bateman), performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:05:01:762
    - RL00160-PD-0025_01, 1939-08-14 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0025_01)
      Title: Young Beichan (Lord Bateman), performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:05:30:757
      Title: Geordie [1st air], performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:25:910
      Title: Geordie [2nd air], performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:55:793
      Title: Gypsie Laddie (Black Jack Davy), performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:02:981
    - RL00160-PD-0025_02, 1939-08-21 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0025_02)
      Title: Father Along, performer: Pittman Brothers, location: Hand, running time: 00:03:15:292
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: Pittman Brothers, location: Hand, running time: 00:04:16:523
      Title: Down In the Garden To Pray (All My Sins Been Taken Away), performer: Pittman Brothers, location: Hand, running time: 00:03:10:044
    - RL00160-PD-0026_01, 1939-08-24 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0026_01)
      Title: Haul Away Joe, performer: Leary, Thomas, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:55:688
      Title: What Shall We Do with a Drunken Sailor?, performer: Leary, Thomas, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:32:518
      Title: Whiskey Johnny, performer: Leary, Thomas, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:37:785
      Title: When Johnny Goes Down to Rilo, performer: Leary, Thomas, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:48:442
      Title: Blow the Man Down, performer: Leary, Thomas, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:38:379
      Title: Hanging Johnny, performer: Leary, Thomas, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:32:082
      Title: Lanky Lucy Lister, performer: Leary, Thomas, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:23:188
      Title: Hullabaloo Balay, performer: Leary, Thomas, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:36:893
      Title: Pretty Polly, performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:56:077
      Title: O Drowsy Sleeper, performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:06:999
    - RL00160-PD-0026_02, 1939-08-24 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0026_02)
      Title: Charming Beauty Bride, performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:48:469
      Title: No Sign of a Marriage, performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:00:202
      Title: William Riley, performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:00:910
    - RL00160-PD-0027_01, 1939-08-24 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0027_01)
      Title: Maid Freed From the Gallows (Go Slacken Your Rope), performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:46:447
      Title: Lord Ullin's Daughter, performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:08:773
      Title: Early, Early In the Spring, performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:01:570
      Title: Young Hunting (Lord Bonnie), performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:41:500
      Title: Bonny Blue Eyes, performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:30:730
    - RL00160-PD-0027_02, 1939-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0027_02)
      Title: Young Johnny, performer: Eggers, Herman A., location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:35:326
      Title: Piggy Wiggy, performer: Eggers, Herman A., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:40:621
      Title: Frog Went A-Courtin', performer: Eggers, Herman A., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:18:908
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: Eggers, Herman A., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:02:013
      Title: Cock Robin, performer: Eggers, Herman A., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:16:547
    - RL00160-PD-0028_01, 1939-08-24 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0028_01)
      Title: Our Good Man, performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:59:044
      Title: Rattlesnake (Nice Young Ma-Wa-Wan), performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:44:855
      Title: George Collins, performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:59:490
      Title: Geordie [Spoken interlude], performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:34:233
      Title: Pretty Saro, performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:25:241
    - RL00160-PD-0028_02, 1939-08-25 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0028_02)
      Title: Had an Old Shoe, performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:40:957
      Title: Maid Freed From the Gallows (Hangman's Tree), performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:34:944
      Title: Pretty Polly, performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:23:583
      Title: I Wish I Was a Mole In the Ground, performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:18:981
      Title: Pretty Fair Maid (The Broken Token), performer: Thomas, Ettie, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:07:767
      Title: Pretty Peggy, O, performer: Thomas, Ettie, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:10:294
    - RL00160-PD-0029_01, 1939-08-26 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0029_01)
      Title: Wife Wrapped Up In Wether Skin (Dandoo), performer: Walker, Edith, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:17:668